solunet-infomex.com 2017-06-06

# 

Privacy Policy for Use of the odovo Account

Owen Media Partners Inc. together with its subsidiaries (“we”, “us”, “OMP“) has created this privacy statement (the “Privacy Policy”) and is firmly committed to the protection of your privacy. This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect, use and secure the personal information of individuals using odovoTM Account (“Site”). This Statement reflects the requirements of Canada's Federal and Provincial privacy legislation as well as our continuous commitment to protecting your personal information.

**BY USING SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY STATEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS STATEMENT, DISCONTINUE ALL USE OF THIS SITE IMMEDIATELY.**  

**1\. Definitions**  
a) Personal information is information about you that uniquely identifies you as an individual. Your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number are all examples of personal information.  However, the name, address and telephone number of an individual that appears in a telephone directory that is available to the public (where such individual can refuse to have such information appears in such directory) does not fall under the scope of “personal information” as it is publicly available information.  
b) A “user” is someone who accesses, browses, crawls or in anyway uses the Site.  The terms “you” and “your” refer to you, as a user of the Site;  
c) “Content” means text, images, photos, audio, video, and all other forms of data or communication.  “Your Content” means Content that you submit or transmit to or through the Site, such as ratings, reviews, compliments, invitations, and information that you display as part of your account profile.  “User Content” means Content that users submit or transmit to or through the Site.  “OMP Content” means Content that we create and make available on the Site.  "Third Party Content" means Content that is made available on the Site by parties other than OMP or its users.  "Site Content" means all of the Content that is made available on the Site, including Your Content, User Content, Third Party Content, and OMP Content.  

**2\. Information we collect about you**  
2.1 When you create a odovoTM account, we ask for and store information about you, such as your name, nickname, email address, and signup location. We use your nickname to create your account name, and we use your signup location to help target the Site to the town you live in. We use your email address to send you updates, provide services to you in connection with the Site. We may store Your Content, display it to other users, and use it for promotional purposes. Note that if you include personally identifiable information in Your Content, it can be used and viewed by others. We are not responsible for the information you choose to include in Your Content.  
2.2 We automatically store information related to your use of the Site, such as the pages you view on the Site, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, browser language, referring URL, and the date and time of your visit. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.  
2.3 OMP may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data from your hard disk or cookie files created by other websites. OMP does not correlate this information with data about individual users, nor does it share this information or sell it to any third party.  We only use cookies to tailor the visitor's experience to the Site. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser.  
2.4 We may use software that receives and records the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer that has contacted OMP Websites. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting OMP Websites.  

**3\. Use of Information**  
3.1 We collect information from users primarily to facilitate their participation in the Site. Specifically, usernames and passwords allow registrants to access the Site; and names and email addresses are helpful for communicating with users. The other information helps us tailor the content of our Site to user preferences and communicate information about other products or services that might be of interest.  
3.2 We may use your personally identifiable information in other ways in connection with our business; for example, we may use the information to alert you to improvements to the Site and solicit your opinion about such improvements.  We use non-personally identifiable information in an aggregate, anonymous manner primarily to (i) improve the design, functionality, and content of our Properties; and (ii) provide products and services that might interest our users.  
3.3 Personal information may be shared with our agents or contractors in connection with services that they perform for us. Our written agreements with such agents and contractors ensure that personal information can only be used for the purposes for which it was shared with them, and that they handle the personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Some of our agents and contractors are located outside of Canada and, as such, are subject to foreign laws, including laws that may require disclosure of personal information to government agencies in those countries.  
3.4 If you post content for public view on the Site, we may distribute Your Content to a wider audience by sharing it (or portions of it) with third parties so that they can publish it on their own websites and media platforms. We may ask them to credit you as the source of these contributions by including your account name and profile photo.  
3.5 We may use personal information for routine administrative purposes, such as investigating abuses on the Site, responding to user inquiries and enforcing and applying our Terms and Conditions.  

**4\. Safeguards and Retention**  
4.1 We use physical, organizational and technological safeguards to protect your personal information against theft, loss or unauthorized access, use, modification, disclosure or disposal. However, given that electronically submitted data is not 100% secure, we make no warranties as to the security of any personal information you submit online, which you do at your own risk.  

**5\. Third-party websites**  
5.1There are a number of places on our website where you may click on a link to access other websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement or a search result on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These third-party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend that you consult the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit by clicking on the "privacy" link typically located at the bottom of the webpage you are visiting.  

**6\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
6.1We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the e-mail address you most recently provided us in your odovo account (unless we do not have such an email address), and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to inform yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.  

**7\. Access and Contact**  
7.1 You have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your odovo account. Upon written request, OMP will provide you access to your personal information, subject to certain exceptions as provided by the applicable legislation. If you notice any errors or omissions in your personal information, please advise us in writing and we will promptly correct them where appropriate. If you have concerns regarding our Statement, the security of your personal information or our compliance with the applicable personal information protection legislation, please send a brief explanation of your concern to our Privacy Officer at: 

Privacy Officer  
Owen Media Partners Inc.  
1599 Hurontario Street, Suite 301  
Mississauga, L5A 4G1  
ON, CANADA  
privacy@owen-media.com
